ANKITA NAGPAL

7922 5th Avenue, Apt 2, Brooklyn, NY 11209 | 585-503-1687 | an2846@nyu.edu|https://www.linkedin.com/in/ankita-nagpal/

SUMMARY

First-year master degree student at New York University with specialization in Computer Science, actively seeking internship opportunities for Summer 2019. Four years of valuable experience working in major computer software domain. Experienced in modern programming languages and frameworks, I have led end-to-end production of deliverables related to Adobe Experience Manager, automation of Adobe Analytics, dashboards and templates and more. I want to use my professional skills and academic background to contribute directly to the growth of the organization and strongly desire to continue improving my own skills to grow in my career.

EDUCATION

New York University, Tandon School of Engineering, New York, NY

Master of Science, Computer Science

Indira Gandhi Delhi Technical University for Women (IGDTUW), Delhi India

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science

TECHNICAL SKILL

Programming: C++, C, JAVA, Python
Web Designing: HTML, CSS, JavaScript
Database: MvSOL. MongoDB

Framework: Struts, Flask, Java Selenium and TestNG, Cucumber Other: Adobe Experience Manager (AEM), Git, Jenkins

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Adobe Systems, Noida, India *Senior Software Engineer*

May 2015-August 2018

Anticipated: May 2020

June 2014

- Worked on Adobe Experience Manager (AEM), for Community Help and Learn (CHL) team which provides Support, Help and Learn content for all Adobe products on website.
- Led end-to-end delivery for new templates for websites in terms of functionality and customer experience, localization, code review for all the functionality changes.
- Integrated Analytics tracking on webpages like custom link tracking and feedback and verbatim text on https://helpx.adobe.com/support.html pages using Dynamic Tag Management (DTM).
- Developed an analytics automation dashboard using Flask framework to view the expected tracked events being sent to Adobe Analytics.
- Worked on various Chrome extensions and scripts for day-to-day production enhancement.
- Created and updated automated test cases in Java Selenium framework, maintaining smoke and regression test cases.
- Attended project training and knowledge transfer at Adobe headquarters in San Jose and San Francisco.

Samsung India Electronics (SRI-Noida), Noida, India

July 2014- May 2015

Software Engineer

- Analysed Production issues for Samsung smartphones, feature phones and tablets. Confirmed software for market issues, OS upgrade (Lollipop), and production for SWA/EUR/MEA regions.
- Managed security solutions (KNOX) for Samsung mobiles and tablets that enable business and personal content to coexist on the same handset.

Center for development of Advanced Computing (C-DAC)

Ministry of Communication and Information Technology, Noida, India

Intern

June 2013 –August 2013

• Undertook a Project titled e-Claim Reimbursement to be used by the employees using Struts framework which is based on MVC (Model View Controller) model.

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Secured Routing in Opportunistic Networks

Multi User Chat System

Jan 2014 –May 2014

June 2012 - August 2012